(this["webpackJsonpmy-app"]=this["webpackJsonpmy-app"]||[]).push([[0],{10:function(e,t,r){},12:function(e,t,r){"use strict";r.r(t);var c=r(0),a=r.n(c),n=r(5),s=r.n(n),i=r(2),o=(r(10),r(1));function u(e){var t=e.setUsername,r=Object(c.useRef)();return Object(o.jsxs)("div",{className:"start",children:[Object(o.jsx)("input",{className:"startInput",placeholder:"enter your name",ref:r}),Object(o.jsx)("button",{className:"startButton",onClick:function(){r.current.value&&t(r.current.value)},children:"Start"})]})}function d(e){var t=e.setTimeOut,r=e.questionNumber,a=Object(c.useState)(30),n=Object(i.a)(a,2),s=n[0],o=n[1];return Object(c.useEffect)((function(){if(0===s)return t(!0);var e=setInterval((function(){o((function(e){return e-1}))}),1e3);return function(){return clearInterval(e)}}),[s,t]),Object(c.useEffect)((function(){o(30)}),[r]),s}var m=r(3),l=r.p+"static/media/play.8e5f6d1d.mp3",h=r.p+"static/media/correct.160572d7.mp3",x=r.p+"static/media/wrong.e9468218.mp3";function j(e){var t=e.data,r=e.questionNumber,a=e.setQuestionNumber,n=e.setTimeOut,s=Object(c.useState)(null),u=Object(i.a)(s,2),d=u[0],j=u[1],b=Object(c.useState)(null),f=Object(i.a)(b,2),O=f[0],p=f[1],v=Object(c.useState)("answer"),w=Object(i.a)(v,2),y=w[0],N=w[1],q=Object(m.a)(l),g=Object(i.a)(q,1)[0],S=Object(m.a)(h),$=Object(i.a)(S,1)[0],I=Object(m.a)(x),k=Object(i.a)(I,1)[0];Object(c.useEffect)((function(){g()}),[g]),Object(c.useEffect)((function(){j(t[r-1])}),[t,r]);var T=function(e,t){setTimeout((function(){t()}),e)};return Object(o.jsxs)("div",{className:"trivia",children:[Object(o.jsx)("div",{className:"question",children:null===d||void 0===d?void 0:d.question}),Object(o.jsx)("div",{className:"answers",children:null===d||void 0===d?void 0:d.answers.map((function(e){return Object(o.jsx)("div",{className:O===e?y:"answer",onClick:function(){return!O&&function(e){p(e),N("answer active"),T(3e3,(function(){N(e.correct?"answer correct":"answer wrong")})),T(5e3,(function(){e.correct?($(),T(1e3,(function(){a((function(e){return e+1})),p(null)}))):(k(),T(1e3,(function(){n(!0)})))}))}(e)},children:e.text})}))})]})}var b=function(){var e=Object(c.useState)(null),t=Object(i.a)(e,2),r=t[0],a=t[1],n=Object(c.useState)(!1),s=Object(i.a)(n,2),m=s[0],l=s[1],h=Object(c.useState)(1),x=Object(i.a)(h,2),b=x[0],f=x[1],O=Object(c.useState)("$ 0"),p=Object(i.a)(O,2),v=p[0],w=p[1],y=Object(c.useMemo)((function(){return[{id:1,amount:"$ 100"},{id:2,amount:"$ 200"},{id:3,amount:"$ 300"},{id:4,amount:"$ 500"},{id:5,amount:"$ 1.000"},{id:6,amount:"$ 2.000"},{id:7,amount:"$ 4.000"},{id:8,amount:"$ 8.000"},{id:9,amount:"$ 16.000"},{id:10,amount:"$ 32.000"},{id:11,amount:"$ 64.000"},{id:12,amount:"$ 125.000"},{id:13,amount:"$ 250.000"},{id:14,amount:"$ 500.000"},{id:15,amount:"$ 1.000.000"}].reverse()}),[]);return Object(c.useEffect)((function(){b>1&&w(y.find((function(e){return e.id===b-1})).amount)}),[b,y]),Object(o.jsx)("div",{className:"app",children:r?Object(o.jsxs)(o.Fragment,{children:[Object(o.jsx)("div",{className:"main",children:m?Object(o.jsxs)("h1",{className:"endText",children:["You earned: ",v]}):Object(o.jsxs)(o.Fragment,{children:[Object(o.jsx)("div",{className:"top",children:Object(o.jsx)("div",{className:"timer",children:Object(o.jsx)(d,{setTimeOut:l,questionNumber:b})})}),Object(o.jsx)("div",{className:"bottom",children:Object(o.jsx)(j,{data:[{id:1,question:"Rolex is a company that specializes in what type of product?",answers:[{text:"Phone",correct:!1},{text:"Watches",correct:!0},{text:"Food",correct:!1},{text:"Cosmetic",correct:!1}]},{id:2,question:"When did the website `Facebook` launch?",answers:[{text:"2004",correct:!0},{text:"2005",correct:!1},{text:"2006",correct:!1},{text:"2007",correct:!1}]},{id:3,question:"Which of the following is observed as Sports Day every year?",answers:[{text:"29 August",correct:!0},{text:"22 April",correct:!1},{text:"26 July",correct:!1},{text:"2 October",correct:!1}]},{id:4,question:"A coin of what value is called as \u201cAthhanni\u201d?",answers:[{text:"1 Rupee",correct:!1},{text:"50 Paise",correct:!0},{text:"25 Paise",correct:!1},{text:"2 Rupees",correct:!1}]},{id:5,question:"Which glacier is the primary source of the river Ganga?",answers:[{text:"Gangotri",correct:!0},{text:"Godwin-Austen",correct:!1},{text:"Pindari",correct:!1},{text:" Siachen",correct:!1}]},{id:6,question:"What is Balushahi a type of?",answers:[{text:"Turban",correct:!1},{text:"paper Art",correct:!1},{text:"Sweet",correct:!0},{text:"Dance Form",correct:!1}]},{id:7,question:"Which of the following gods is also known as \u2018Gauri Nandan\u2019?",answers:[{text:"Agni",correct:!1},{text:"Ganesha",correct:!0},{text:"Indra",correct:!1},{text:"Hanuman",correct:!1}]},{id:8,question:"Which of these terms can only be used for women?",answers:[{text:"Dirghaayu",correct:!1},{text:"Suhagan",correct:!0},{text:"Chiranjeevi",correct:!1},{text:"Sushil",correct:!1}]},{id:9,question:"Where was the BRICS summit held in 2014?",answers:[{text:"Brazil",correct:!0},{text:"India",correct:!1},{text:"Russia",correct:!1},{text:"China",correct:!1}]},{id:10,question:"Which of these are names of national parks located in Madhya Pradesh?",answers:[{text:"Krishna and Kanhaiya",correct:!1},{text:"Kanha and Madhav",correct:!0},{text:"Ghanshyam and Murari",correct:!1},{text:"Girdhar and Gopal",correct:!1}]},{id:11,question:"In the game of ludo the discs or tokens are of how many colours?",answers:[{text:"One",correct:!1},{text:"Two",correct:!1},{text:"Three",correct:!1},{text:"Four",correct:!0}]},{id:12,question:"Which day is observed as the World Standards Day?",answers:[{text:"June 26",correct:!1},{text:"Oct 14",correct:!0},{text:"Nov 15",correct:!1},{text:"Dec 2",correct:!1}]},{id:13,question:"The Indian National Calendar is based on",answers:[{text:"Christian era",correct:!1},{text:"Vikram era",correct:!1},{text:"Saka era",correct:!0},{text:"Hijji era",correct:!1}]},{id:14,question:"Which of the followiing is a folk dance of India?",answers:[{text:"Kathakali",correct:!1},{text:"Garba",correct:!0},{text:"Mohiniattam",correct:!1},{text:"Manipuri",correct:!1}]},{id:15,question:"The dance encouraged and performed from the temple of Tanjore was",answers:[{text:"Odissi",correct:!1},{text:"Bharatnatyam",correct:!0},{text:"Kathakali",correct:!1},{text:"Mohiniattam",correct:!1}]}],questionNumber:b,setQuestionNumber:f,setTimeOut:l})})]})}),Object(o.jsx)("div",{className:"pyramid",children:Object(o.jsx)("ul",{className:"moneyList",children:y.map((function(e){return Object(o.jsxs)("li",{className:b===e.id?"moneyListItem active":"moneyListItem",children:[Object(o.jsx)("span",{className:"moneyListItemNumber",children:e.id}),Object(o.jsx)("span",{className:"moneyListItemAmount",children:e.amount})]})}))})})]}):Object(o.jsx)(u,{setUsername:a})})};s.a.render(Object(o.jsx)(a.a.StrictMode,{children:Object(o.jsx)(b,{})}),document.getElementById("root"))}},[[12,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.7650d116.chunk.js.map